techlazy.com 2013-12-08

# Privacy Policy

techlazy.com understands that privacy is very important to you. The following policy is intended to protect your privacy and ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. We continue to develop our web site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide. As a result, our policies will continue to evolve. By using techlazy.com web site, you consent to our use of guest information as described in this Online Privacy Policy. As we implement new technology and introduce new services, we will update our Online Privacy Policy. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis for our most current privacy policy practices. 

#### What information do we collect?

We and/or third party vendors may collect information from you whenever you visit our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
1\. To personalize your experience.  
(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
2\. To improve our website.  
(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We DO NOT sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 8, 2011
